Well then, get along well
では、仲良く
After that, we become friends...
な ってから仲良くなっていきます...
why
なんで
How did you take the photo?
どう やって撮った?
どうやって撮った?
How did you take the photo?
It’s been a while, right?
久 しぶりだよね?
Where did you take the photo?
どこに撮った?
Isn't it good?
いいじゃない?
I can't say it.
言えないです
Can't you say it?
言えない?
How did you take the photo?
どうやって撮った?
good.
いい
yeah?
ん?
What did you do?
何しちゃった
of?
の?
Don't you speak well when facing this way?
こ っち向きで よく喋らんの?
Let me hear it, a fairy tale.
声させるか、おとぎ
Shagame.
しゃ がめ
Bring out the bell.
ベルを出して
Mom, will you stay?
お母さん、残る?
This video is.
この動画は
No.
ダメです
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
yes.
はい
What should I do?
どうする?
Well then.
じゃあ
I listen carefully.
よく聞きます
That's right.
そうやな
Shall I squat?
しゃがむか
Here, touch this too.
ほら、こっちも触れ
Yeah.
うん
Did you hear that?
聞いたの?
Did you finish your punishment in Japan today?
今日、日本でお仕置き終わった?
Shall we have a sarpy?
サーピーしようか?
Yeah.
うん
What's your reply?
返事は?
Yeah.
うん
Fairy tales that are played indoors in Japan.
日本で中でするおとぎ
That's good.
いいっすよね
Can I cum inside you?
中出してでいい?
Yeah.
うん
What's your reply?
返事は?
Mom, why aren't you playing?
お母さん、なんで遊んないの?
yes.
はい
Hey?
なあ?
Yeah.
うん
I hope you hear it.
聞いてもらわんと
Yes, I say Rika.
はい、リカですって言って
Yeah.
うん
I'm doing an Instagram live now.
インスタライブしてるから、今
Hey?
なあ?
Look.
ほら
Then, take measures.
じゃあ、対策して
Yeah.
うん
Why are you making me lick your dick?
なんでおチンコを舐めさされてるのか、
Shall I squat?
しゃがむか
Can you tell me?
言ってみ?
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Hey.
なあ
Where did you move this?
どこで動かしたの、これ
Like this, like this.
こうやって、こうやって
Yeah.
うん
Oshinya.
おしにゃ
Hey.
なあ
Raise the inside.
中を上げて
I can't see it under the wall.
壁の下で見えない
Yes, look here.
はい、こっち見て
Is this how it works?
こうやって動かしてるのか?
Ah.
な あ
Let's do this like this.
こうやってこうやろうよ、これ
Oh, wow.
あ、やば
Yes, come on.
はい、きそ
It's coming out a lot.
めっちゃ出てるじゃん
Should I go up and give it another shot?
上に行って、もう一発やるか
Hey.
なあ
Well then, let's have sex properly.
じゃあ、ちゃんとハメ出しよっか
Hey, have fun.
なあ、楽しく
For this one.
こっち向け
I said it was an invitation to consent.
同意の誘いですって言って
It is an invitation to consent.
同意の誘いです
If you start acting strange, your mom will get angry right away.
変な動きしたら、すぐお母さんに怒るぞ、
this.
これ
Hey.
なあ
There's a DVD version of this in the town where I live.
住 んでる町とかに、これ、DVDバラマックあるな
got it.
わかりました
It's surprising, but should I consider releasing it?
意外とだけど、出すと考えちゃいいですか
Did you understand?
分かったか
yes.
はい
Well then, let's have fun, Riga-chan.
じゃあ、楽しくやろうか、りがちゃん
Just page it out and see.
ペーって出してみ、ほら
That's cute, Riga-chan.
かわいいじゃん、りがちゃん
Hey.
なあ
Did you have sex?
ハメちゃった?
yes.
はい
There was a lost child.
迷子が出てたじゃん
How many cup breasts are there?
おっぱい、何カップだっけ?
I'm a D cup.
Dカップです
D cup?
Dカップ?
That's good.
いい じゃん
Where do you feel the most?
どこが感じやすいの?
Chikubi.
チクビ
Chikubi?
チクビ?
Well then, let's do Chikubi for 30 minutes.
じゃあ、チクビ30分やってやろうか
Hey.
なあ
What should I do?
どうする?
Look here.
こっち見て
Shall we do Chikubi for 30 minutes?
チクビ30分やる?
What will happen?
どうなっちゃう?
I can't stand it.
耐えれないです
picture?
え?
I can't stand it.
耐えれないです
Why why?
なんでなんで?
Can't go home?
帰れない?
I can't stand it.
耐えれないです
Can't stand it?
耐えれない?
Well then, let's do it.
じゃあ、やっちゃおうか
I will answer your request properly.
リクエストにちゃんと答えてあげる
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
Do you want to do it with your mom?
お母さんと一緒にやっちゃう?
I don't like it.
嫌です
why?
なんで?
picture?
え?
I'll give it to my mom.
俺、お母さんにやってあげるから
No.
ダメです
No?
ダメ?
So, Rika-chan, will you take my place?
じゃあ、りかちゃん、身代わりになる?
yes.
はい
This is so naughty.
やらしいですね、これ
That's a cute cat.
かわいいお猫じゃん
Hey.
ね え
It's cute.
かわいいです
So cute.
かわいいて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
terrible?
やばい?
What would you like me to do?
何やられたらいい?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
Shall I touch you a little?
ちょっと触ってあげようかな?
Yeah.
うん
Hey?
なあ?
Yeah.
うん
What should I do?
どうする?
Decide for yourself?
自分で決める?
I want you to touch me.
触ってほしいです
Do you want me to touch you?
触ってほしいの?
yes.
はい
Don't talk.
喋るなあ
I'm not moving.
私、動きが振ってるな
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
this.
これ
It's cute.
かわいいね
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃかわいいな
Don't worry.
平気して
I have to be here when I go properly.
ちゃんと行く時に、こっちに居なきゃダメだよ
Looks like I'm going.
行きそうです
Have you gone?
行っちゃった?
Yeah.
うん
Kozaki says he won't forgive me for something like this.
小崎は、こんなんで許してくれないのよって
I'm scared so I'll just put it in there.
こわいさって入れちまおうか
It looks pretty scary.
ずいぶん、こわいさそうじゃん
I love you, dick.
ちんこ、好きなんだよ
It's facing this way.
こっちに向いてるのよ
Yeah.
うん
It's flowing normally now.
もう、正常で流れしますから
No, it was the other day.
違う、こないしだ
Would you like me to cum inside you?
いっぱい中に出してもらおうか
yes.
はい
Then I'll enter next time.
じゃあ次、俺が入れるわ
Understood?
わかった?
yes.
はい
thank you.
ありがとう
This came out inside.
中に出ちゃったね、これ
What should I do?
どうする?
Well then, why don't you do it with me next time?
じゃあ次、俺とやろっか
Hey.
なあ
There's no way I'll do it, I'll do it.
やるわけねえ、やるわ
Mama, I'll take command.
おまちゃん、私は指揮しておこうよ
yes.
はい
Did you understand?
わかったんか?
yes.
はい
Well, it's interesting.
まあ、やもしろいわね
As punishment, I'll take this photo.
罰としては、この写真撮ろうからな
Understood.
わ かった
Okay.
いいっしょ
ERROR
この撮影、合意でしたって言え
Okay.
よし
Well then, I'll come tomorrow as well.
じゃあ、明日もちゃんと来いわ
yes.
はい
Understood?
わかった?
yes.
はい
Well then, let's go ahead.
じゃあ、お先行くぞ
Yeah.
うん
See you then.
じゃあな